Guide to the Loveday Yates Sketches of Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Loveday Yates sketches of Yale University
1940-1950
RU 640
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
(1 box)
The collection consists of pencil and charcoal drawings depicting scenes of Yale and New Haven, Connecticut drawn by Loveday Yates in the 1940s and 1950s.
Yates, Loveday
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Biographical / Historical
Loveday Yates was a security monitor in Sterling Memorial Library at Yale during the 1940s and 1950s.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of pencil and charcoal drawings depicting scenes of Yale and New Haven, Connecticut drawn by Loveday Yates in the 1940s and 1950s.
New Haven (Conn.) -- Pictorial works; Drawings (visual works); Yates, Loveday; Yale University -- Pictorial works
- Sketches, circa 1940-1950; Series I
  - Branford College, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Chapel -lamp, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dwight Hall -chapel, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Elm Street -winter morning, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elm Street -winter morning [in color], circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Green -churches in winter, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Harkness Tower, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Old Campus, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sterling Memorial Library -circulation desk, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Courtyard, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Entrance (interior), circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Interior, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Interior, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Interior, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Nave, circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Rare Book Room (now Manuscripts and Archives), circa 1940-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)